Guide to the Arthur E. Scott photograph collection, 1910-1976
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Events, 1921-1976; (Boxes 9-11, 23-25, 27, 30, 33, 35-36, 38-42)
  - Subseries 3.5: Inaugurations, 1956-1974
    - Coolidge, Calvin, Inauguration, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
      2 negatives; March 4, 1925, reproduced from Interional New Photo collection
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., Inauguration, January 21, 1957 (Box 24)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., Oath of Office, December 6, 1973 (Box 24)
    - Harding, Warren G., Inauguration, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
      10 negatives; March 4, 1921, reproduced from National Archives collection
    - Hoover, Herbert C., Inauguration, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
      9 negatives; March 4, 1929, reproduced from International News Photo collection
    - Javits, Jacob, Oath of Office, January 9, 1963 (Box 24)
      2 negatives; includes Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., Inauguration, January 20, 1965 (Box 24)
    - Kennedy, John F., Inauguration, January 20, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Lincoln, Abraham, Inauguration, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
      2 negatives; March 4, 1961, reproduced from National Archives collection
    - Murray, Joseph, Federal Home Loan Board, Oath of Office, May 3, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Oath of Office, December 19, 1974 (Box 24)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, Inauguration, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
      2 negatives; March 4, 1905, reproduced from International News Photo collection
    - Tower, John, Oath of Office, June 15, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Unidentified inaugurations, 1940s-1960s (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, Oath of Office, Inauguration, 1950s-1960s (Box 24)
      7 negatives; March 3-4, 1917, reproduced from International News Photo collection
    - Nixon, Richard M., Inauguration, January 20, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, John F., Inauguration, January 20, 1961 (Box 36)
      35mm negatives
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., Oath of Office, December 6, 1973 (Box 38)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., Inauguration, January 20, 1965 (Box 41)
      2 1/2 inch strips
  - Subseries 3.6: Buddy Poppy, 1929-1942
    Subseries 3.6 contains photographs of politicians and celebrities receiving Buddy Poppies from the Veterans of Foreign Wars.
    - Ashurst, Henry F., 1930s (Box 25)
    - Austin, Warren R., 1941 (Box 25)
    - Ball, Joseph H., April 9, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Bunker, Berkeley L., April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Burton, Harold H., 1941, April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Byrnes, James, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Capper, Arthur, 1941, April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Caraway, Hattie, 1938, 1941 (Box 25)
    - Connally, Thomas (Tom), 1930s (Box 25)
    - Dieterich, William H., 1935 (Box 25)
    - Dingell, John, April 10, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Downey, Sheridan, 1941, April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Edison, Charles, 1940 (Box 25)
    - Garner, John N., 1935 (Box 25)
    - George, Walter, 1941, April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Green, Theodore, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Greenway, Isabella, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Harrison, Byron Patton (Pat), 1935 (Box 25)
    - Hatch, Carl, 1941 (Box 25)
    - Healy, Arthur, April 10, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Herring, Clyde L., April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Lesinski, John, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Maloney, Francis, 1942 (Box 25)
    - McNary, Charles, 1941 (Box 25)
    - Nye, Gerald F., April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - O'Day, Caroline, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Overton, John H., April 10, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Patman, Wright, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Roosevelt, Henry L., 1935 (Box 25)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1935, April 9, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Schulte, William, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Truman, Harry S., April 9, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Unidentified, 1930s-1940s (Box 25)
    - Van Nuys, Frederick, April 9, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Wallace, Henry, 1941, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Walsh, David I., 1935 (Box 25)
    - White, Wallce, Jr., April 9, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Wiley, Alexander, April 8, 1942 (Box 25)
    - Woodring, Harry, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Hoover, Herbert C., 1929-1933 (Box 27)
    - Rogers, Will, 1930s (Box 27)
  - Subseries 3.7: Miscellaneous Events, 1921-1976
    Subseries 3.7 contains photographs of events that do not fit into other subseries, such as funerals, parades, and protests.
    - Bicentennial, July 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Includes photographs of the Magna Carta on loan from England
    - Biddle, William P., funeral, March 1923 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Bonus Army, 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Boy Scouts of America National Jamboree, June 30-June 7, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      First National Jamboree
    - Conference on the Limitation of Armament, November 12, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - "Devil Dog" (Marines) Parade, White House, October 7, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Elephants at the U.S. Capitol building, 1960s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Embassy of France reception for French President, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 5)
      "Mrs. William Randolph Hurst Jr. at French Embassy for French President, with her are Wm. McCracken and Martha Roundtree."
    - Hunger Marches, 1931-1933 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Events- parades, funerals, 1930s-1940s (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Services for Unkowns of World War II and Korea, May 20, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Sigsbee, Charles D., funeral, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Taft, William Howard, funeral, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - AEC [Atomic Energy Commission] Bureau Standards, May 14-15, 1958 (Box 25)
    - Alexandria, Virginia hospital fundraiser, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - Alfalfa Club annual outing, June 17, 1939 (Box 25)
    - Atomic Cannon Test, Frenchman Flat, Nevada, May 25,1953 (Box 25)
    - Bible Translation Day, September 30, 1966 (Box 25)
      7 negatives; includes Fred Harris, Benjamin Reifel
    - Bicentennial committee, July 22, 1975 (Box 25)
      1 negative; includes John Warner, Charles H. Percy
    - Elephants at the U.S. Capitol building, August 21, 1964, November 30, 1971 (Box 25)
      9 negatives; includes James G. Beal, Hugh D. Scott, Richard S. Schweiker, Charles M. Mathias, Jr.
    - Jepson Hotel Supply Company, opening, April 26, 1958 (Box 25)
    - National Training School for Boys, 1930s (Box 25)
    - Tanker refuel, June 28, 1957 (Box 25)
      2 negatives; KC-135 jet tanker prepares to refill B-52
    - Virginia Little Theatre, 1940s-1950s (Box 25)
      90 negatives
    - Bremen Flyers, 1920s (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; first east to west Trans-Atlanic mail package
    - Congress Opening, 1920s (Box 27)
    - Sousa, John Philip, funeral, March 1932 (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, funeral, February 6, 1924 (Box 27)
    - Unknowns lie in state, placed in Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, Arlington National Cemetery, March 29-30, 1958 (Box 40)
    - Hearings on undecided New Hampshire Senate seat election, January 1975 (Box 41)
      2 1/2 inch strip negatives
    - Hoover, Herbert C., lies in state, October 23, 1964 (Box 42)
- Series 4: Art, Publications, Reference Materials, 1918-1976; (Boxes 11, 25, 27, 35, 38)
  This series contains photographs of newspapers and art, as well as reference publications and correspondence. This series is divided into the following subseries:
  - Subseries 4.1: Images of Newspapers, 1918-1962
    Subseries 4.1 contains photographs newspapers and other publications.
    - Congress map, June 19, 1961 (Box 25)
      3 negatives; states to gain and lose Congress seats
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., inaugurated, January 21, 1953 (Box 25)
    - Merrill, Dick and Jack Lambie ocean flight, May 15, 1937 (Box 25)
    - Missile mail, June 8, 1959 (Box 25)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., reelected, November 4, 1936 (Box 25)
    - Sanborn, Kay, "Founders of Freedom", October 22, 1962 (Box 25)
      18 negatives
    - Truman, Harry S., Proclamation 2714, December 31, 1946 (Box 25)
    - Washington, George, inauguration drawings, February 20, 1932 (Box 25)
    - Battle of Gettysburg, New York Times, 1910s-1920s (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; July 3, 1863
    - Illustrated California News, The, First Edition, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1910s-1920s (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; September 1, 1850
    - Lincoln, Abraham, assassinated, New York Herald, 1910s-1920s (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; April 15, 1865
    - Pershing, John J., leads army, New York Times, September 13, 1918 (Box 27)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, dies, New York Herald, January 7, 1919 (Box 27)
    - Tunney, Gene, keeps boxing title, New York Times, September 23, 1927 (Box 27)
  - Subseries 4.2: Art, 1933-1959
    Subseries 4.2 contains photographs of art work.
    - Elephant logo and drawings, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - George Gordan Meade Memorial, 1930s (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Memorial by Charles Grafly
    - Miscellaneous Artwork, 1930s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Includes Suffrage Monument by Adelaide Johnson
    - Samuel Gompers Memorial, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Pulaski, Casimir, drawings and statue, 1930s-1940s (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Cox monuments [Thomas Jefferson], 1930s-1940s (Box 25)
    - Dollhouse, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - Levine, Jack, "Welcome Home", June 11, 1959 (Box 25)
    - Mitchell, Billy, statue at Smithsonian Insitution, December 17, 1957 (Box 25)
    - Mellate [Christian artwork], 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - "Shield of Freedom, The", December 19, 1956 (Box 25)
    - Stained glass window, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - Tower, [Lou], silverware, other artwork, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    - [Asian] artwork, 1960s-1970s (Box 35)
    - [Asian] artwork, 1960s-1970s (Box 38)
  - Subseries 4.3: Reference Publications and Correspondence, 1932-1976
    Subseries 4.3 contains reference publications and correspondence relating to photographs in the collection.
    - Congressional Record Vol. 119, no. 191, December 6, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Gerald R. Ford takes oath as Vice President pages H10855, S22132
    - Correspondence, notes/captions, 1950-1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Inauguration Program, Virginia Governor Mills E. Godwin, January 12, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "Miracle Gardens" Spring 1971 issue (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Senator Margaret Chase Smith on the cover; includes note from Senator Smith
    - Newspaper clippings, 1932-1964 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Presidential Portraiture Collection brochure; staff of Republican Conference, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - "Supreme Court Chamber 1810-1860" pamphlets, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Includes invitation to Dedication of Supreme Court Chamber
    - "Virginia Political Greats" report by A. E. Scott, May 1976 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Series 5: Scrapbooks, 1918-1946; (27 volumes)
  This series contains scrapbooks created by Arthur E. Scott. Most items contained within the scrapbooks are newspaper clippings, many of which depict photographs taken by Scott.
  - Seventh Street explosion, Washington, D.C., Novermber 22, 1929 (Volume 1)
  - Reporters jailed, later honored, for protecting sources on speakeasies, December 11-12, 1929 (Volume 1)
  - Junior Post section, art work of Arthur E. Scott age 16 "The Vikings 1000 AD", December 29, 1929 (Volume 1)
  - First picture Arthur E. Scott published in a newspaper: Eddie Rickenbacker receiving Congressional Medal of Honor, November 7, 1930 (Volume 1)
  - Jules Bledsoe "colored" baritone recital, Show Boat star, April 15, 1931 (Volume 1)
  - Amelia Earhart photograph, undated (Volume 1)
  - May Queen at American University, May 9, 1932 (Volume 1)
  - Photographs taken while Scott was a copyboy at the Washington Times, May 1932 (Volume 1)
  - Mills Brothers photograph, signed, October 15, 1932 (Volume 1)
  - White House photographer identifications, 1934-1948 (Volume 1)
  - House of Representative's photographer identifications, 1934-1948 (Volume 1)
  - Various press passes, undated (Volume 1)
  - First Washington Times-Herald assignment, rubber bathing suits, undated (Volume 1)
  - Real estate and other advertisement photographs by Arthur E. Scott, 1933 (Volume 1)
  - "Our Gang" child actor "Chubby" photograph, September 9, 1933 (Volume 1)
  - 1933 World Series, Washington Senators vs. New York Giants, Arthur E. Scott's first job for International News Photos, box score, press passes, October 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt at first World Series game in Washington, D.C., October 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - Steve Early and Mrs. Early with Franklin D. Roosevelt, October 6, 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - Richard Byrd's Polar plane in Washington, D.C.; aerial photographs taken from plane, October 12, 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - Photograph of Arthur E. Scott mixing darkroom chemicals, October 12, 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - H.M.S. Duane in Washington Navy Yard, November 6, 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - John J. Pershing presents Douglas MacArthur with a medal, November 30, 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - National Cheese Week, Department of Agriculture, December 12, 1933 (Volume 2A)
  - Photographs of Arthur E. Scott with International New Photos assignment lists and expenses, 1933-1934 (Volume 2A)
  - Naval Affairs Committee, first assignment for committee on Capitol Hill, January 23, 1934 (Volume 2A)
  - New Japanese ambassador, Honorable Hiroshi Saito, February 12, 1934 (Volume 2A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt at podium, undated (Volume 2A)
  - Air Mail hearings, March 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt departs Washington, D.C. to fish in Florida, March 28, 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Anne Lindbergh receives Hubbard Medal from National Geographic Society, April 1, 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Renovated Russian Embassy opens, April 10, 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Arthur E. Scott expenses, April-September 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Horseback riding along Chesapeake shore, undated (Volume 2B)
  - Union parades (painters, iron workers, bricklayers), September 3, 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Dick Powell, signed photograph, undated (Volume 2B)
  - Redemption division of the U.S. Treasury, September 28, 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Leo Carrillo, actor (Pancho), 1934 (Volume 2B)
  - Arthur E. Scott expenses, December 1934-March 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt and Eleanor Roosevelt dinner with John N. Garner and Mrs. Garner, January 17, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt at Tenth Annual Conference on the Cause and Cure of War, January 23, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Arthur E. Scott with Eleanor Roosevelt (background of picture), undated (Volume 3A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt smiling, March 6, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Roosevelt family dinner with Eleanor Roosevelt, President Franklin D. Roosevelt, Mrs. James Roosevelt (FDR's mother) and Gus Gennerich, secret service man, March 9, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Investigation of the death of heiress Elva Statler, Mrs. H. Bradley Davidson, March 9, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Arthur E. Scott wedding to Grace Ladson of Clarendon, Virginia, undated (Volume 3A)
  - Huey "Kingfish" Long, April 27, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Richard E. Byrd reception on S.S. Bear, May 9, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Ringling Brothers Circus, cowboy Tim McCoy on horse, May 21, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., June 5, 1935 (Volume 3A)
  - Amelia Earhart testifies for unregulated flying, May 1935 (Volume 3B)
  - Howard C. Hopson, utilities magnate, testifies before house committee, August 19, 1935 (Volume 3B)
  - Stratford Hall, October 16, 1935 (Volume 3B)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt lays a wreath at the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier in Arlington National Cemetery, undated (Volume 3B)
  - Edith Maxwell murder trial, with photographs of Arthur E. Scott, November-December 1935 (Volume 3B)
  - 74th Congress convenes; Franklin D. Roosevelt gives anti-big-business speech, January 4, 1936 (Volume 4A)
  - J. P. Morgan, January 1936 (Volume 4A)
  - Photos of ambassadors, undated (Volume 4A)
  - Benefit horse show for Purcelleville Library Building fund, August 6, 1936 (Volume 4A)
  - Norfolk, Virginia flooding, September 1936 (Volume 4A)
  - Noel Coward and Gertrude Lawrence, December 1, 1936 (Volume 4B)
  - Edith Maxwell murder trial with attorney Charles H. Smith of Alexandria, Virginia, December 1936 (Volume 4B)
  - Arthur E. Scott's presidential inauguration passes, January 20, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - John L. Lewis, chairman of the Committee of Industrial Organization, January 23, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - Lincoln Memorial, 128th Birthday celebration for Abraham Lincoln, with Franklin D. Roosevelt, February 13, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - Tallulah Bankhead, February 20, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - General Hugh Johnson, March 23, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - Demonstration at Langley Field, Hampton, Virginia for Congress members, April 24, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - Howard Hughes, undated (Volume 4B)
  - Fannie Bryce and Bobby Clark, new "Ziegfeld Follies", May 11, 1937 (Volume 4B)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt laughing with James Farley, July 4, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - First national Boy Scout Jamboree, July 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - State funeral of Joseph T. Robinson, July 16, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Hugo Black confirmed for U.S. Supreme Court, August 18, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Closing first session of 75th Congress, August 23, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - John L. Lewis, September 4, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Front Royal, Virginia house of Mrs. George Barnett where Duke and Duchess of Windsor may stay, October 23, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Richard E. Byrd decorated, October 23, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt dedicates new Federal Reserve Building, October 21, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Stephen Early, press secretary for Franklin D. Roosevelt, November 3, 1937 (Volume 4C)
  - Hahn's shoe store fire, Washington, D.C., December 13, 1937 (Volume 5A)
  - United States postage stamp manufacturing, March 15, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution president, Mrs. William A. Becker, calls conference to order, April 19, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars petitions members of Congress to keep America out of war, April 27, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Special Senate and House committee investigates Tennessee Valley Authority, May 26, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - John L. Lewis, chairman of the Committee of Industrial Organization with Senators, May 2, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Signed silhouettes of politicians by Arthur E. Scott, June 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, profiles from fireside chats, June 25, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Gichner Iron Works, July 15, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - Howard Hughes as National Press Club, July 21, 1938 (Volume 5A)
  - National Training School for Boys, September 19, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - Charles Evan Hughes signed photograph, undated (Volume 5B)
  - University of Virginia vs. Navy football game, October 9, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - Inter American Horse Show, October 23, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - Army tank training, air and artillery, October 29, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - District of Columbia Home for the Aged and Infirm, November 8, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - Canadian Trade Treaty with Franklin D. Roosevelt and Cordell Hull, November 14, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - Senate Finance Committee hearings on profit-sharing, November 21, 1938 (Volume 5B)
  - Arthur E. Scott taking squirrel close-up, January 8, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - Felix Frankfurter confirmation hearings for U.S. Supreme Court, January 10, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - 150th anniversary of the commencement of the first Congress of the United States under the Constitution, March 4, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - Portraits of John N. Garner and Mariette Rheiner Garner, by Seymour M. Stone, April 20, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt at Mount Vernon, Virginia, May 5, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - Tallulah Bankhead and her father, William B. Bankhead, June 21, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - George C. Marshall, Chief of Staff, July 18, 1929 (Volume 6A)
  - Fire at U.S. Capitol Building, July 24, 1939 (Volume 6A)
  - John L. Lewis before House Labor Committee, July 27, 1939 (Volume 6B)
  - Film promotion on Edith Cavell at RKO Keith's, September 9, 1939 (Volume 6B)
  - Neutrality legislation, October 1939 (Volume 6B)
  - Cigar series, November 14, 1939 (Volume 6B)
  - Jackson Day Dinner with John N. Garner and Franklin D. Roosevelt, January 8, 1940 (Volume 6B)
  - Actor Raymond Massey in "Abe Lincoln in Illinois", January 22, 1940 (Volume 6B)
  - Scott and Gene Autry, signed photograph, January 1940 (Volume 6B)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, composite head made at A.A.A. broadcast, March 8, 1940 (Volume 6B)
  - George C. Marshall observes Military Affairs Committee on sale of warplanes to Allies, March 27, 1940 (Volume 6B)
  - Unveiling of painting depicting the signing of the Constitution in the U.S. Capitol building rotunda, May 29, 1940 (Volume 6B)
  - Margaret Chase Smith sworn in, eighth woman in Congress, June 10, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Burke-Wadsworth Selective Training and Service Act, conscription bill, August-September 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - William B. Bankhead funeral, Franklin D. Roosevelt attends, September 16, 140 (Volume 6C)
  - Samuel T. Rayburn fills William B. Bankhead's position, September 25, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Confederate Veterans annual reunion in Washington, D.C., October 8, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Testing new camouflaged uniforms, October 24, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - John L. Lewis pledges to resign if Franklin D. Roosevelt wins a third term, October 25, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt campaign schedule with journalist assignments, November 1, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt returns to the White House after his election, November 7, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Oscar Hammerstein, December 11, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt calls for defense build-up, December 29, 1940 (Volume 6C)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt inauguration, January 20, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Henry A. Wallace, January 21, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Retiring ambassador Joseph P. Kennedy at hearing for lease-lend bill to aid Great Britain, January 21, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Former governor John G. Winant of New Hampshire as possible successor to position of ambassador to Great Britain, January 23, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Charles Lindbergh before Senate Foreign Relations Committee with Arthur E. Scott in the photograph, February 6, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Joe Lewis vs. Max Baer boxing match, with ticket, May 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Parachute training, July 30, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Camp A. P. Hill training shots, August 19, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt trip to Hyde Park with Arthur E. Scott on the list, October 16, 1941 (Volume 7A)
  - Training shots and munitions factory, February/December 1943 (Volume 7A)
  - Camp Holabird, Maryland, motorcycles, April 8, 1943 (Volume 7A)
  - Camp Lejeune, North Carolina, women in service, June 16, 1943 (Volume 7A)
  - Glider training, August 1943 (Volume 7A)
  - Field first aid and hand to hand combat training, undated (Volume 7A)
  - Red Fox Tavern, Middleburg, Virginia, filming movie, August 17-20, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - Soldiers on "Ninth Street", Washington, D.C., September 6, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - Women guards at the U.S. Treasury, September 7, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - "Back the Attack" War Show, September 13, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - Junior Army Navy Guild Organization (JANGO), September 27, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - U.S. Capitol building sightseeing, October 6, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - The Greenbrier/Ashford General Hospital, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, October 19, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - Women flyers; Arthur E. Scott in a plane, October 22, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - National Press Club, November 15, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - United Nations Service Center, November 22, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - Henry Major, caricaturist, visits Congress, December 15, 1943 (Volume 7B)
  - George C. Marshall, color cover shots, undated (Volume 7B)
  - Treasury Department series, Arthur E. Scott burning bills to light his cigar, January 18, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - Celebrity shots: Jinx Falkenburg, Red Skelton, Lucille Ball, Walter Pidgen, Brian Dulvey, February 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt birthday celebrations, January 29, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - Physical therapy aides at Walter Reed Hospital, Washington, D.C., February 9, 1944 (Volume 8A)
  - Mount Vernon, Virginia series, February 19, 1944 (Volume 8A)